[MUSIC]
>> You say you love me, but you never beat me.
You always promise, but you never date me.
I try to fax, but it's busy always.
I try to land work, but you crash the gateway.
You never spend your nights with me.
You don't go out with other girls either.
You only love your collider.
I fill your screen with hearts and roses.
I fill your mail file with lovely phrases.
They all come back invalid user.
You never let me into your computer.
You never spend your nights with me.
You don't go out with other girls either.
You prefer your collider.
I give you a golden ring to show you my love.
You want to stick it in a printed circuit.
To fix a voltage leak in your collector.
To plug my feelings into your detector.
You never spend your nights with me.
You don't go out with other girls either.
You only love your collider.
Your collider.